greenmomsmeet.com 2019-04-04

# Privacy Policy - Moms Meet

MomsMeet.com aims to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs, and, at the same time, we want to protect your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Website.

Your use of this Website is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions. Your use of this website constitutes acknowledgment of this Privacy Policy. In addition to carefully reviewing this Privacy Policy, please carefully review our Terms and Conditions for use of this Website.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or wish to inquire about or correct your personally identifiable information that we have collected, please contact our Privacy Policy coordinator by e-mail at info@momsmeet.com, or send your inquiries by mail to:

Privacy Policy Coordinator  
MomsMeet.com  
104 Centre Blvd, Suite A  
Marlton, NJ 08053

In order to protect your privacy and for security reasons, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to or modifying your information.

**WHO WE ARE**  
May Media Group LLC is the registrant of this website.

**WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU**  
This website may ask adults that create a member account, subscribe to our publication(s), make purchases on this website, participate in our Sampling Programs, surveys, contests, sweepstakes and other offerings, to provide certain personal information, including name, mailing address, e-mail address and phone number. Participants may optionally provide additional information which may include, age, gender, education, marital status, etc. The type of information requested is specifically tailored to the particular offering (e.g. number of children in household, preferences for food products, healthcare, etc.). We may also collect information from you if you contact us for customer service issues. The identifiable information we collect is used for internal purposes only.

We also collect photos and information provided by you in our Feedback Surveys. You have the option to opt out of having these photos shared publicly while filling out the survey.

If you make purchases on this website, we also collect credit card, financial and billing information from you.

The information we collect from you is stored indefinitely.

**HOW WE USE INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU**  
All credit card, financial and billing information that we collect is used solely in connection with payment for your purchases from this Website. We use the information you supply through this Website to provide you with the information, product, or service you requested, to enhance your experience on this Website, and for internal business purposes consistent with this policy. For example, if you subscribe to any of our publications, or make purchases on this Website, we may use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation notice and your mailing address to send you your purchases, or, if you enter one of our contests, we will use this information to notify you if you won. We may also use the information to tell you about publications, products or services that we believe will interest you, or improve existing services and product offerings by tailoring them to your interests. We also share certain information with our affiliates in order to better situate their products and services for market. The information shared with these affiliates includes but is not limited to anonymous data provided during a Feedback Survey for a Sampling Program. It does not include your individual information but may use your first name and last initial.   

While your individual information (personally identifiable information) is protected as described in this privacy policy, we reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as finding compatible advertisers and partners and analyzing usage trends.

**SHARING INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES**  
May Media Group LLC does not sell, share or distribute any personal information with third parties, except as described in this Privacy Policy.

Certain third parties may need access to your information for the sole purpose of providing you the product or service you requested. For example, if you purchase products through this Website, we may forward your information to third parties for services such as credit card processing and order fulfillment. We may provide a third party with your first and last name and mailing address in order to send you a shipment for a Sampling Program that you have opted into.

We never sell or share your e-mail address or other individual information with third parties.

Your information may also be disclosed if the law requires us to do so in connection with investigations or other legal proceedings. This includes but is not limited to sharing information with third parties for fraud protection.

**THIRD-PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS**  
We may provide your information to our third-party service providers. However, our Privacy Policy does not cover information collected on those third-party sites, and these third-party companies are not bound by our Privacy Policy. Always consult the other site’s privacy policies before providing any information on those sites, as May Media Group, LLC does not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties.

**OPT-OUT**  
If you do not wish to continue to receive email solicitations from May Media Group, LLC, you may opt-out by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the email, or, by sending an email to info@momsmeet.com with the word “UNSUBSCRIBE” in the subject line. Please allow 10 business days for your request to take effect.

**TECHNOLOGY WE USE**  
This Website uses “cookies” to enhance your online experience. A “cookie” is a data file containing user-specific information that a website transfers to the user’s computer. Cookies help us keep track of your patterns and preferences so that we may improve the content and offerings on our Website. For example, we may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you enter our site, and to offer you products or services you may like.

Cookies alone do not contain personally identifiable information, such as name, e-mail address, etc. However, once you furnish such personally identifiable information through our Website, this information may be linked to the information stored in the “cookie.”

We may also use “web beacons,” log files, or similar technologies to collect non-personal aggregate information such as browser type, operating system, Internet protocol (IP) addresses, Internet service provider (ISP), platform type, pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data.

Some of our advertisers may use cookies, web beacons, log files, and similar technologies as well, which are subject to each advertiser’s own privacy policies, not ours, and May Media Group LLC disclaims all liability in connection therewith.

You may be able to control the use of cookies by modifying your Web browser to reject cookies. However, if you do that, some portions of this Website may not function properly.

this Website automatically identifies your “IP Address” which is the unique location where you entered the Internet (e.g. the computer at your desk at work). We collect IP Addresses and use them to keep track of broad demographic statistics, like how many people visit our site, and to diagnose problems with our server or to administer our Website.

**SECURITY**  
We have security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the data under our control. When the Website is accessed using Internet Explorer versions 6.0 or higher, or a comparable internet browser, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology protects information using both server authentication and data encryption to help ensure that data is safe, secure, and available only to you.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**AFFILIATE MARKETING LINKS**

We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.

**CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**  
We do not collect any personally identifiable information from children.

**CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**  
This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time, and the date of the most recent revision will appear at on this page. Your continued access to this Website constitutes your acceptance of any changes or revisions to our Privacy Policy.

Updated: May 25, 2018
